<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">QEng Tour</string>
    <string name="line1">Welcome to the Queen\'s University Tour! To get started, tap the \'Take the Tour\' button!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="button1">Take the Tour</string>
    <string name="button2">Map of Campus</string>
    <string name="button3">Gallery</string>
    <string name="button4">Pro Tips</string>
    <string name="button5">F.A.Q.</string>
    <string name="button6">Links and Contacts</string>
    <string name="title_activity_guided_tour">Take the Tour</string>
    <string name="title_activity_campus_map">Map of Campus</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fun_facts">Fun Facts</string>
    <string name="title_activity_faq">Frequently Asked Questions</string>
    <string name="title_activity_links_and_contacts">Links and Contacts</string>
    <string name="title_activity_google_map_of_campus">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_list_of_gallery">ListOfGallery</string>
    <string name="EngTitle">Engineering Buildings</string>
    //Strings for Links and Contacts Page    <string name="TitleContactsPage">Links and Contacts</string>
    <string name="GenInfo">General Information</string>
    <string name="C1"> Corrine Hoas</string>
    <string name="Info1">corrine.hoas@queensu.ca</string>
    <string name="C2"> Main Reception</string>
    <string name="Info2">reception@appsci.queensu.ca</string>

    <string name="VisandInfoCent">Visitor and Information Centre</string>
    <string name="C4">Email: jduc@queensu.ca </string>
    <string name="Info4">Phone: 613-533-2794 \nHours of Operation:\nMon - Fri (9:00 AM - 5:00 PM)\nSat - Sun (10:00 AM - 4:00 PM)</string>

    <string name="EngQandInfo">Engineering Questions and Information</string>
    <string name="C6">Email: engineering.first.year@queensu.ca</string>
    <string name="Info6">Phone: 613-533-6000 - Ext. 74092\nOffice: Room 300 Beamish-Munro Hall (ILC)</string>
    <string name="Useful">Useful Links</string>
    <string name="StuBlog"><a href="http://prospective.appsci.queensu.ca/Student-Bloggers.html">Student Bloggers (Life as an Engineer at Queens University)</a>\n \n<a href="http://issuu.com/queenseng/docs/parentguide?viewMode=presentation">Parents Guide to Queen\'s Engineering and Applied Science</a>\n\n<a href="http://www.queensu.ca/studentexperience/summer-orientation-soar">Summer Orientation to Academics and Resources (SOAR) 2015</a>\n\n<a href="http://www.queensu.ca/registrar/financials/tuition-fees">Information on Tuition and Fees</a></string>
    <string name="Social">Social Media</string>
    <string name="Info11">Join the <a href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/QueensU2020/">Queen’s University Class of 2020</a> Facebook Group!\n\nLike the <a href="https://www.facebook.com/QueensEngineer">Faculty of Engineering and Applied Science</a> Facebook Page!\n\nFollow <a href="https://twitter.com/queensu">@QueensU</a> on Twitter to receive updates from Queen’s University!\n\nFollow <a href="https://twitter.com/QueensEngineer">@QueensEngineer</a> on Twitter to receive updates from the Faculty of Engineering and Applied Science!\n</string>
    //FAQ Strings    <string name="TitleFAQPage">Frequently Asked Questions</string>
    <string name="EngFAQ">Engineering:</string>
    <string name="UniFAQ">University Life:</string>
    <string name="Q1FAQPage">Q) What courses will I be taking in my First Year?</string>
    <string name="A1FAQPage">A) In First Year, students take a total of 11 courses. 10 are Half-Year courses, and 1 is a Full Year course.\n\n&#8226; FALL \n- APSC 100 (Module 1)\n- APSC 111 (Mechanics)\n- APSC 131 (Chemistry and Materials)\n- APSC 151 (Earth Systems and Engineering)\n- APSC 171 (Calculus I) \n \n&#8226; WINTER \n- APSC 100 (Module 3)\n- APSC 112 (Electricity and Magnetism)\n- APSC 132 (Chemistry and its Applications) \n- APSC 172 (Calculus II) \n- APSC 174 (Introduction to Linear Algebra)\n\nStudents in the general stream also take APSC 161 (Basic Engineering Graphics) in the fall, and APSC 142 (Computer Programming for Engineers) in the winter, while, students in the ECE Innovation stream take APSC 142 in the fall, and APSC 161 in the winter. APSC 100 (Module 2) is broken up amongst students in both the Fall and Winter Term.</string>
    <string name="Q2FAQPage">Q) Do I get to take any complementary studies courses?</string>
    <string name="A2FAQPage">A) Students are required to receive at least 18.75 credits through completion of Complementary Studies Courses. These courses are taken in Upper Years, and can be from Engineering Economics, Communications, Humanities and Social Sciences, Linkage and Professional Issues, Performance Arts and Languages, and Management. These courses are different from the technical electives that students must also take. </string>
    <string name="Q3FAQPage">Q) Do I get to choose my courses this summer on SOLUS?</string>
    <string name="A3FAQPage">A) All First Year Engineering courses are core courses, meaning you must take and pass them in order to complete your degree. These courses are added into your schedule by the faculty. You are also assigned a section and subsection. You do not need to choose any courses in the summer unless you wish. Schedules will be posted on SOLUS sometime before the Fall Term begins. </string>
    <string name="Q4FAQPage">Q) What if I do not do well in my first term?</string>
    <string name="A4FAQPage">A) Queen’s University offers a back up plan called “J-Section”. If any student fails a course, has a GPA below 1.6 , or wants to improve their overall GPA, they can sign up for J-Section. Over the first few weeks of Winter Term, you retake your specified Fall Term courses and sit for exams during reading week. After this, you begin your Winter Term Classes, finishing sometime at the beginning of June. There is an additional fee required to be in J-Section. </string>
    <string name="Q5FAQPage">Q) What is this English Proficiency Test I hear about?</string>
    <string name="A5FAQPage">A) The English Proficiency Test is a written test that all engineering students are required to take and pass to obtain their degree. It is ideally completed in First Year, but is available for students to retake during each exam period over 4 years. </string>
    <string name="Q6FAQPage">Q) Are there private places I can go to work on campus?</string>
    <string name="A6FAQPage">A) Students can go to Stauffer Library and Douglas Library to do work in a private area, with access to many books, articles, and other information. Beamish Munro Hall (ILC) also has numerous study rooms available to be booked for group projects, or individual work. </string>
    <string name="Q7FAQPage">Q) When do I get to choose my engineering discipline and sub-plan?</string>
    <string name="A7FAQPage">A) The different engineering faculties hold discipline nights between January and February to educate students of the many advantages of each specific plan. Students are required to choose their plan for second year at the end of February in their First Year. </string>
    <string name="Q8FAQPage">Q) Is Frosh Week mandatory?</string>
    <string name="A8FAQPage">A) Frosh Week is a great opportunity for students to be introduced to the spirit and excellence of the Engineering Faculty at Queens. Students are put through a variety of events that test teamwork, skills, and passion. Though Frosh Week is not mandatory, it is suggested that incoming students attend events to see what Engineering is all about. With such highly coveted events, Frosh Week 2015 is a week you will definitely not want to miss!</string>
    <string name="Q9FAQPage">Q) What if I cannot afford to pay for Frosh Week events but I still want to participate?</string>
    <string name="A9FAQPage">A) The Engineering Society awards a financial bursary that covers part of the fee of Frosh week for incoming students who require assistance. In order to qualify for this, students must download, complete, and send in the, ‘Frosh Bursary Application Form’. </string>
    <string name="Q10FAQPage">Q) Where can I use my Meal Plan?</string>
    <string name="A10FAQPage">A) If you are living in residence, your first year meal plan can be used at any of the cafeterias, as well as any retail location on campus. You cannot use your meal plan off campus.</string>
    <string name="Q11FAQPage">Q) I am worried about walking alone around campus at night. What services are available?</string>
    <string name="A11FAQPage">A) If you need to get somewhere on campus late at night, Queen’s has a safety service called Walkhome. This service allows any student to call and request a walk, in which a team of one male and one female student staff member will come to your location and safely accompany you as you walk to your destination. Walkhome is completely anonymous and non-judgemental, as staff members do not have a uniform or anything indicating that they work for the service.</string>
    <string name="Q12FAQPage">Q) Does it cost money to take the bus in Kingston as a Queen’s student?</string>
    <string name="A12FAQPage">A) A small fee of your student fees goes to Kingston Transit. Simply show the driver your student card when you get on, and you won’t have to pay any additional fee or bus fare for the whole year. </string>
    <string name="Q13FAQPage">Q) What recreational facilities are available to students?</string>
    <string name="A13FAQPage">A) As part of your student fees, you are provided with access to the workout facilities in the Athletics and Recreation Centre (ARC). Additionally, the gyms, fields, courts, and swimming pool can be reserved upon request.</string>
    <string name="Q14FAQPage">Q) Where can I go if I am ever feeling sick?</string>
    <string name="A14FAQPage">A) If you ever feel sick, you can visit either the Kingston General Hospital (KGH) or the LaSalle Building, both of which are on campus. KGH is located at 76 Stuart Street and the LaSalle Building is located at 146 Stuart Street. It is important to note that you may not skip an exam or test unless you have proof of an illness, personal issue, or serious injury. Thus, if you believe you are too sick to write, you must have a doctor’s note. This is also the case for some labs as well.</string>


    //Tips Settings
    <string name="TitleTipsPage">Pro Tips from Ex-First Years</string>
    <string name="tip1">Don’t fall behind in your classes early on. Although there are no midterms the first few weeks, you should really try and keep up with all your course material because it is very difficult to catch up once you are behind.</string>
    <string name="tip2">Get involved in clubs in your first year! Queen’s provides a wide variety of extra-curriculars for students to take part in.</string>
    <string name="tip3">Although it is important to work hard, it’s also important to have a little fun. Remember to take some time to enjoy yourself while you are here!</string>
    <string name="tip4">You’ll be required to complete an Excel/Word assignment by the first week of classes. Complete this before orientation week! You don’t want to be sitting in your room working while everyone else is having the time of their lives!</string>
    <string name="tip5">Especially in the first term, many professors offer their lecture notes online for you to access electronically or print and annotate in class.</string>
    <string name="tip6">EngSoc offers printed lecture slides for APSC 131 and APSC 132, the two chemistry courses taken in first year. They are sold at a reasonable price and are well worth the money.</string>
    <string name="tip7">Even for courses that provide online lecture notes, be sure to listen to your professors in class. More often than not, they give helpful tips that you won’t find in your notes!</string>
    <string name="tip8">Make some friends in your lectures and tutorials! You’ll really value this decision when you end up missing class from illness or because you couldn’t wake up for your 8:30 lecture.</string>
    <string name="tip9">Learn to compromise. It is very likely that you won’t be able to complete all your readings and finish every homework problem. Try to prioritize your tasks and be as efficient as possible with assignments and studying.</string>
    <string name="tip10">Once work comes, the work keeps coming… Enjoy your first few weeks without midterms, because as soon as they come around, you’ll likely have a midterm every week for the next month and a half!</string>
    <string name="tip11">Remember that grades don’t define you as a person. You’re more than your grades say you are, so don’t feel down about your marks!</string>
    <string name="tip12">You’ll never pass 112 frosh.</string>
    //Building Things    <string name="title_activity_google_guided_tour">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_engineering_buildings_menu">EngineeringBuildingsMenu</string>
    <string name="title_activity_non_engineering_buildings_menu">NonEngineeringBuildingsMenu</string>
    <string name="title_activity_food_buildings_menu">FoodBuildingsMenu</string>
    <string name="title_activity_historical_buildings_menu">HistoricalBuildingsMenu</string>
    <string name="title_activity_picture_view_campus_map">PictureViewCampusMap</string>
    <string name="title_activity_picture_view_campus_map2">PictureViewCampusMap2</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_ellis_hall_building">EllisHallBuilding</string>
    <string name="EllisHallLocation">Location: East side of University Avenue (58 University Avenue). </string>
    <string name="EllisTitle">Ellis Hall</string>
    <string name="EllisInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="EllisInfo">Ellis Hall, constructed in 1958, is home to the Department of Civil Engineering, the Queen\’s Observatory, the GeoEngineering Centre, and the Groundwater and Flows Research Groups. The observatory houses a 16-inch state-of-the-art telescope used to study astrophysics. Ellis Hall is also home to multiple classrooms and an auditorium, where many first year engineering lectures are held. </string>
    <string name="EllisFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="EllisFact">Ellis Hall was one of the first engineering buildings at Queen\’s University to be built away from the north-east portion of campus. Ellis Hall also houses new and innovative classrooms, with interactive displays and unique seating arrangements, both of which allow for increased group work and participation. These classrooms are used for APSC 100 (Engineering Practice) Module 1, a first year engineering course based on group projects. </string>
    <string name="title_activity_chernoff_hall_building">ChernoffHallBuilding</string>
    <string name="ChernoffTitle">Chernoff Hall</string>
    <string name="ChernoffHallLocation">Location: South side of Bader Lane (90 Bader Lane).  </string>
    <string name="ChernoffInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="ChernoffInfo">Chernoff Hall, home to the Department of Chemistry is a new and innovative building composed of both classrooms, laboratory and administrative based sections, and an auditorium/lecture hall. </string>
    <string name="ChernoffFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="ChernoffFact">Chernoff Hall was built with a substantial contribution from Michael and Dorine Chernoff. Both he and his wife also created the, \‘Chernoff Family Award\’, which offers financial assistance to students around Canada who wish to attend Queen\’s University.  </string>
    <string name="title_activity_clark_hall_building">ClarkHallBuilding</string>
    <string name="ClarkTitle">Clark Hall</string>
    <string name="ClarkHallLocation">Location: East side of Fifth Field Company Lane (30 Fifth Field Company Lane). </string>
    <string name="ClarkInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="ClarkInfo">Clark Hall, home to the Campus Bookstore, the Golden Words newspaper head office, and the Clark Hall Pub, was built between 1949 and 1951 with finances paid entirely by engineering students. Clark Hall Pub is located in the top of the building, run by the Engineering Society, and serves as an inviting gathering spot for all students in applied science and other faculties. </string>
    <string name="ClarkFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="ClarkFact">Clark Hall Pub, first opened as a place for students and faculty to correlate recreationally. With the highly riveting, \‘Ritual\’ occurring every Friday afternoon, Clark Hall Pub\’s weekly events still serve as long standing traditions amongst members of the engineering faculty. </string>
    <string name="title_activity_dupuis_hall_building">DupuisHallBuilding</string>
    <string name="DupuisTitle">Dupuis Hall</string>
    <string name="DupuisHallLocation">Location: Attached to the north side of the ILC (19 Division Street). </string>
    <string name="DupuisInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="DupuisInfo">Dupuis Hall is home to the department of Chemical Engineering, the Campus Computer Sales and Service Store, and the ITServices Main Office. Dupuis Hall contains two classrooms and one auditorium as well as multiple laboratory rooms focused on chemistry research. </string>
    <string name="DupuisFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="DupuisFact">Dupuis Hall was constructed in 1966 and is named after Nathan Fellowes Dupuis, a professor of math at Queens in the early 20th century, also a founder of the Faculty of Engineering and Applied Science. </string>
    <string name="title_activity_goodwin_hall_building">GoodwinHallBuilding</string>
    <string name="GoodwinTitle">Goodwin Hall</string>
    <string name="GoodwinHallLocation">Location: Attached to the east side of the ILC (25 Union Street).  </string>
    <string name="GoodwinInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="GoodwinInfo">Goodwin Hall is home to the department of Mining Engineering. It was built in 1972 and it was named after William Lawton Goodwin, the first director of the School of Mining and Agriculture, which is the modern day Faculty of Engineering and Applied Science. There are two major classrooms in Goodwin Hall. </string>
    <string name="GoodwinFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="GoodwinFact">The department of Mining Engineering was the first active department in what evolved into the Faculty of Engineering and Applied Science. Goodwin Hall also houses the School of Computing. In June of 2002, a 20 kilowatt solar array was installed on Goodwin\’s roof. It was constructed as a learning, teaching, and research tool for Applied Science students. The array produces 18,000 kWh of electricity annually, which is distributed among Walter Light Hall, Goodwin Hall, and the Integrated Learning Centre. </string>
    <string name="title_activity_ilcbuilding">ILCBuilding</string>
    <string name="ILCTitle">Integrated Learning Centre</string>
    <string name="ILCLocation">Location: Northeast corner of Union and Division Street (45 Union Street). </string>
    <string name="ILCInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="ILCInfo">The Integrated Learning Centre (ILC) is home to the Faculty of Engineering and Applied Science. It is also called Beamish-Munro Hall.  In addition, the building consists of group rooms, a multimedia facility, a site investigation facility, a design studio, and a prototyping studio and lab facilities. Beamish-Munro Hall was built to meet the needs of a growing multi-disciplinary Engineering faculty, as a model of sustainable construction. </string>
    <string name="ILCFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="ILCFact"> Beamish-Munro Hall was named in honor of Robert Beamish (Sci\’60) and Donald Munro (Sci\’52). In 2005, a year after opening, it was selected as one of the most environmentally advanced buildings in Canada. The ILC is a student-oriented building that was designed in collaboration with students. It serves as a resource to broaden awareness of green building design and environmental sustainability. The facility itself is instrumented as a working laboratory, where students can see structural elements of the building that are usually hidden and monitor systems like air quality, heating, lighting, and cooling using specially designed software, showing how sustainable practices can be incorporated into building design. Inside the front doors is a green wall that filters particles from the air before it is distributed throughout the building. Since 2004, it has won a numerous number of awards.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_innovation_commons_building">InnovationCommonsBuilding</string>
    <string name="ICTitle">Innovation Commons</string>
    <string name="ICInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="ICInfo">The Queen\’s Innovation Commons is a new 70,000 square-foot complex that the University is planning to launch to condone graduate students innovative ideas and creations. This building will serve as a cohesive and collaborative learning environment that will help students succeed from an entrepreneurial standpoint. Special laboratories, offices, classrooms, machinery, and equipment will be made available to students to support their learning and expansion of their academic knowledge. The QIC is a new approach to teaching and designing, where students and faculty members have the opportunity to work out complex solutions to dignified problems. The Queen\'s Innovation Commons will be equipped with world renowned design studios to support graduate students in their research. Students need to have opportunities and resources available to them to think critically and thrive in the workplace, and that is what the aim of the QIC is. The post-secondary world is a competitive environment, but with the help of the Queen\’s Innovation Commons, graduate students will have the chance to have their ideas flourish and grow, with support from team members and colleagues. </string>
    <string name="title_activity_mclaughlin_hall_building">MclaughlinHallBuilding</string>
    <string name="MclaughlinTitle">Mclaughlin Hall</string>
    <string name="MclaughlinHallLocation">Location: South edge of University Avenue (130 Stuart Street). </string>
    <string name="MclaughlinInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="MclaughlinInfo">McLaughlin Hall contains 3 classrooms and is home to lectures for Engineers. Additionally, many engineering design teams build their projects in McLaughlin Hall. It is home to the department of Mechanical Engineering. </string>
    <string name="MclaughlinFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="MclaughlinFact">McLaughlin Hall was completed in 1948. It was built on the site of the old Observatory. A story is told that Chancellor Dunning obtained the funds for McLaughlin hall by passing a note at a board meeting to Col. McLaughlin, which said “Queen\’s needs a new mechanical engineering building.”</string>
    <string name="title_activity_miller_hall_building">MillerHallBuilding</string>
    <string name="MillerTitle">Miller Hall</string>
    <string name="MillerHallLocation">Location: South edge of Division Street (36 Union Street). </string>
    <string name="MillerInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="MillerInfo">Miller Hall, constructed in 1931, is home to the Department of Geological Sciences and Geological Engineering, as well as the Miller Museum of Geology. Miller Hall was greatly expanded in 1973, with the construction of the Bruce Wing. </string>
    <string name="MillerFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="MillerFact">Miller Hall hosts many rocks and minerals, as can be learned from APSC 151 (Earth Systems and Engineering), a first year engineering course discussing mainly geology. </string>
    <string name="title_activity_stirling_hall_building">StirlingHallBuilding</string>
    <string name="StirlingTitle">Stirling Hall</string>
    <string name="StirlingHallLocation">Location: South side of Bader Lane (64 Bader Lane). </string>
    <string name="StirlingInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="StirlingInfo">Stirling Hall is the distinctive round building, home to the Departments of Physics, Engineering Physics, and Astronomy. It contains many lecture halls as well as a range of smaller rooms used for labs and tutorials.  </string>
    <string name="StirlingFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="StirlingFact">A notable feature of the building is a Foucault Pendulum, which hangs in the center of the second floor. The pendulum swings in a pattern and at a speed determined by the rotation of the earth and the latitude of Kingston.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_walter_light_building">WalterLightBuilding</string>
    <string name="WalterTitle">Walter Light Hall</string>
    <string name="WalterHallLocation">Location: North side of Union Street between Barrie and Division (19 Union Street).  </string>
    <string name="WalterInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="WalterInfo">Walter Light Hall is home to the department of Electrical and Computer Engineering (ECE). The fifth floor of the building includes an Information Processing and Communication Laboratory (IPCL). The research goals of the laboratory are to impact and influence the next generations of wireless communication systems and their application. It provides a unique research training experience for graduate students. In addition to the lab\’s own work, they also collaborate with other laboratories at Queen\’s, as well as, several other laboratories in Canada, such as the Communications Research Centre in Ottawa. </string>
    <string name="WalterFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="WalterFact">An interesting feature of the building is that every floor is connected to Goodwin Hall. </string>
    <string name="title_activity_ban_building">BanBuilding</string>
    <string name="BanRighTitle">Ban-Righ Cafeteria</string>
    <string name="BanRighLocation">Location: South-west corner of University Avenue and Bader Lane (10 Bader Lane). </string>
    <string name="BanRighInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="BanRighInfo">Ban Righ Dining Hall is the second largest dining hall on campus. Like Leonard Hall, Ban Righ offers a buffet-style service featuring nutritious entrees, desserts and more. </string>
    <string name="BanRighFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="BanRighFact">Vegetarian and special dietary options are available during every meal, and the Queen\’s Food site allows students to view weekly menus online. Ban Righ is not open on weekends. </string>
    <string name="title_activity_lazy_building">LazyBuilding</string>
    <string name="LazyTitle">The Lazy Scholar</string>
    <string name="LazyLocation">Location: Lower level of Victoria Hall (75 Bader Lane). </string>
    <string name="LazyInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="LazyInfo">The Lazy Scholar is located in the basement of Victoria Hall, and serves as a retail food outlet and cafe for students, especially first years. Featuring flat screen TVs, pool tables, ping pong tables, a fireplace, and a comfortable lounge, the Lazy Scholar is the go to place for interaction amongst friends. </string>
    <string name="LazyFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="LazyFact">The Lazy Scholar often holds events such as open mic nights, accepts meal plans, and is open late during the week for those night time studying snacks! </string>
    <string name="title_activity_leonard_building">LeonardBuilding</string>
    <string name="LennyTitle">Leonard Hall Cafeteria</string>
    <string name="LennyLocation">Location: West end of Bader Lane (150 Queen\’s Crescent). </string>
    <string name="LennyInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="LennyInfo">Leonard Dining Hall is a student cafeteria on campus. It provides new daily menu options, such as the vegan station, pizza bar, soup and salad bar and more. </string>
    <string name="LennyFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="LennyFact">Leonard Cafeteria is the largest dining hall on Queen\’s campus with over 650 seats. Special lunches and dinners are scheduled regularly at different times throughout the week. For those with a meal plan (mainly first years), this is a great place to grab food. </string>
    <string name="L21Title">Location 21</string>
    <string name="L21Location">Location: Corner of Albert and Stuart Street (222 Stuart Street).</string>
    <string name="L21InfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="L21Info">Location 21 is the newest retail location on campus. It has a "Build Your Own Salad Station", fresh cut deli meats and cheeses.</string>
    <string name="L21FactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="L21Fact">Location 21 has Queen\'s University\'s first Coca-Cola® Freestyle Machine!</string>
    <string name="BenidicksonTitle">Agnes Benidickson Field</string>
    <string name="BenidicksonLocation">Location: South side of Fleming Hall, Kingston, Ontario. </string>
    <string name="BenidicksonInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="BenidicksonInfo">Agnes Benidickson Field (AB Field) is a beautiful garden and recreational area to view and walk/sit in.</string>
    <string name="BenidicksonFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="BenidicksonFact">The field is named after Agnes McCausland Benidickson, the first woman Chancellor at Queen\'s University. AB Field is also the main location of Engineering Orientation Week activities and events. </string>
    <string name="GrantTitle">Grant Hall</string>
    <string name="GrantLocation">Location: East side of University Avenue (43 University Avenue).</string>
    <string name="GrantInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="GrantInfo">Grant Hall seats 900 people and is used for meetings, lectures, concerts, ceremonies, dances, and exams.</string>
    <string name="GrantFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="GrantFact">Grant Hall is Queen\'s best-known landmark because of its tall limestone clock-tower. It is named after Queen\'s most important principal a national figure, George Monro Grant. In addition, Grant Hall was used as a military hospital during WWI and an entertainment centre and dining hall during WWII.</string>
    <string name="NicolTitle">Nicol Hall</string>
    <string name="NicolLocation">Location: South side of Union Street between University Avenue and Fifth Field Company Lane (60 Union Street).</string>
    <string name="NicolInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="NicolInfo">Nicol Hall is home to many departments in the Faculty of Engineering and Applied Science.</string>
    <string name="NicolFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="NicolFact">Nicol Hall has historical significance since it was used as an army barracks in WWI. The building was named after former professor William Nicol, who also donated funds for building construction.</string>
    <string name="KingstonTitle">Kingston Hall</string>
    <string name="KingstonLocation">Location: Just south of Grant Hall (103 Stuart Street).</string>
    <string name="KingstonInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="KingstonInfo">Kingston Hall was originally built to provide classroom and library space for the Faculty of Arts and Science. Currently, the hall is home to many of the Queen\'s language departments.</string>
    <string name="KingstonFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="KingstonFact">This building is named after the City of Kingston because they donated the funds for its construction. Along with Grant Hall, which is attached to Kingston Hall, the building served as a military hospital during WWI and as a training barracks for army courses in WWII.</string>
    <string name="SummerhillTitle">Summerhill</string>
    <string name="SummerhillLocation">Location: Just west of Arch Street (55 Stuart Street).</string>
    <string name="SummerhillInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="SummerhillInfo">Since the 1860\'s, Summerhill has been the Principal\'s official residence, although only the east wing is now used for that purpose.</string>
    <string name="SummerhillFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="SummerhillFact">Summerhill is the oldest building at Queen\'s and originally housed the entire university. Prior to this, when Kingston was the capital of Canada in the early 1840s, the building was actually rented as a home to MPs. Over the course of its history, Summerhill has been used to house students, classrooms, the library, and even a gymnasium at one point. The east wing of the building was recently renamed Agnes Benidickson House in honour of the former Chancellor.</string>
    <string name="TheologicalTitle">Theological Hall</string>
    <string name="TheologicalLocation">Location: The south end of Fifth Field Company Lane (85 Stuart Street).</string>
    <string name="TheologicalInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="TheologicalInfo">Theological Hall houses the School of Religion and the Department of Drama. It is the third oldest building on campus.</string>
    <string name="TheologicalFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="TheologicalFact">With money donated by Kingston citizens, Theological Hall was built as the university\'s main building throughout the late 19th century. Also around this time, the building became known as the "Old Arts Building" while Kingston Hall was the "New Arts Building." Theological Hall was actually fireproofed after a large fire took place in Kingston Hall in the early 1930s.</string>
    <string name="ARCTitle">Athletics and Recreation Centre</string>
    <string name="ARCLocation">Location: Just north of University Avenue and Union Street (284 Earl Street).</string>
    <string name="ARCInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="ARCInfo">The Queen\’s Centre is a newly built common complex that serves as a community gathering place. It is home to the Athletics and Recreation Centre (ARC), the Drugs Mart Pharmacy, The Common Ground, The Grocery Checkout, retail food outlets, and rentable room spaces for clubs, rehearsal, and academics. The building incorporates academics and recreational activities, and calls all members of the community to its modern compound. </string>
    <string name="ARCFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="ARCFact">The ARC is a highly modern and developed recreation centre, being equipped with a 38 x 25 metre pool, gym, squash/racquetball courts, fitness rooms, aerobic/weight rooms, and designated class areas. </string>
    <string name="DouglasTitle">Douglas Library</string>
    <string name="DouglasLibraryLocation">Location: South-east corner of University Avenue and Union Street (93 University Avenue).</string>
    <string name="DouglasInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="DouglasInfo">This library provides access to scientific and technical literature, journals, monographs, DVDs and more. Inside, there are study areas, seminar rooms, electronic classrooms and workstations available for users.</string>
    <string name="DouglasFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="DouglasFact">The current library collection was formed in 1997 when the old Douglas Library was renovated and the collections of 10 engineering and science libraries were compiled. This resulted in its nickname, \'the engineering library\'. </string>
    <string name="GordonTitle">Gordon Hall</string>
    <string name="GordonHallLocation">Location: South side of Union Street, between University Avenue and Fifth Field Company Lane (74 Union Street).</string>
    <string name="GordonInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="GordonInfo">Gordon Hall is home to the Office of the University Registrar, Career Services, the School of Graduate Studies, the Office of the Associate Vice-Principal and Dean of Student Affairs, Campus Tours, Records and Services, Student Awards, and Undergraduate Admission.</string>
    <string name="GordonFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="GordonFact">Gordon Hall was completed in 1911 as a gift from the government of Ontario. Initially the building was home to the department of Chemistry for over 90 years. Around 2002, the department of Chemistry moved to Chernoff Hall following the completion of its construction.</string>
    <string name="JDUCTitle">John Deutsch University Centre</string>
    <string name="JDUCLocation">Location: North-east corner of Union Street and University Avenue (87 Union Street).</string>
    <string name="JDUCInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="JDUCInfo">The John Deutsch University Centre, constructed mostly in 1947, is home to the Alma Mater Society, the Tricolour Outlet, the Publishing and Copying Centre, Office of the University Rector, Society of Graduate and Professional Students, multiple restaurants, and much more. The Alma Mater Society is the student government at Queen\’s and its office is located in the centre. The Tricolour Outlet is the best place for finding Queen\’s attire, as well as purchasing a bus ticket to go home aboard the Tricolour Express.</string>
    <string name="JDUCFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="JDUCFact">The way nearly every Queen\’s student refers to the John Deutsch University Centre is “The JDUC” (pronounced jayduck). There is a Tim Horton\’s in the basement of the JDUC that always has a much smaller line than the one in the ARC (just north of the JDUC).</string>
    <string name="MacCorryTitle">Mackintosh-Corry Hall</string>
    <string name="MacCorryLocation">Location: Beside Tindall field and behind Ellis Hall (68 University Avenue).</string>
    <string name="MacCorryInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="MacCorryInfo">Mackintosh-Corry Hall (abbreviated to Mac-Corry) is a very large and multi-purpose hall constructed in 1973. It is home to many departments belonging to the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, as well as the Mac-Corry Cafe. The Cafe features multiple food choices, including the Great Canadian Grilling Company, a favorite for burgers. </string>
    <string name="MacCorryFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="MacCorryFact">Mac-Corry is affectionately referred to as “The Maze” due to its size and confusing layout. Due to its length, Mac-Corry is a great building to walk through to class during the winter.</string>
    <string name="NixonTitle">Nixon Field</string>
    <string name="NixonLocation">Location: East side of University Avenue between Union Sreet and Stuart Street.</string>
    <string name="NixonInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="NixonInfo">Nixon Field serves as both the home turf of Queen\’s rugby and a general recreational field for students. Due to its close proximity to Kingston Hall, Nixon Field is also known as Kingston Field.</string>
    <string name="NixonFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="NixonFact">In April 2011, Kingston Field was rededicated as “Nixon Field” in recognition of a generous pledge from former Queen\’s students Gordon (BCom\’79) and Janet Nixon (BCom\’80). Nixon Field is located on the former militia parade grounds and ordnance lands of the British garrison.</string>
    <string name="StaufferTitle">Stauffer Library</string>
    <string name="StaufferLibraryLocation">Location: North-east corner of university and Union (101 Union Street).</string>
    <string name="StaufferInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="StaufferInfo">Stauffer Library is the largest library on campus with study and research space for more than 1,200 students. It houses the university\’s humanities and social sciences collections. Stauffer Library is a 5 story building, and there are many other services available such as meeting rooms, maps, air photos, seminar and training rooms, and information services.</string>
    <string name="StaufferFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="StaufferFact">As such a huge building would require funding, the $48-million facility was a Queen\’s Challenge Campaign initiative that was funded by the government of Ontario and the private sector. The largest donation towards the library came from the Joseph S. Stauffer Foundation and therefore, the building was named in honor of Joseph S. Stauffer. In 1997, Stauffer Library was awarded the Governor General\’s Award for Architecture.</string>
    <string name="TindallTitle">Tindall Field</string>
    <string name="TindallLocation">Location: South side of Union Street, between University Avenue and Albert Street.</string>
    <string name="TindallInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="TindallInfo">Located just northeast Victoria Hall and beside Mackintosh-Corry Hall, Tindall Field is a full-sized, multi-season playing field surrounded by a three-lane rubberized jogging track.</string>
    <string name="TindallFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="TindallFact">Tindall Field is named after Queen\’s legendary football coach, Frank Tindall. The field was originally located directly behind Victoria Hall, but was moved to its present location in 2008 because of a new underground parking garage and surface lot beside it.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_arcbldg">ARCBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_douglas_bldg">DouglasBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_gordon_bldg">GordonBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_jducbldg">JDUCBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_mac_corry_bldg">MacCorryBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_nixon_field_bldg">NixonFieldBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_stauffer_bldg">StaufferBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tindall_bldg">TindallBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_benidickson_bldg">BenidicksonBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_grant_hall_bldg">GrantHallBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_nicol_hall_bldg">NicolHallBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_kingston_hall_bldg">KingstonHallBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_summerhill_bldg">SummerhillBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_theological_hall_bldg">TheologicalHallBldg</string>
    <string name="JefferyTitle">Jeffery Hall</string>
    <string name="JefferyHallLocation">Location: West side of University Avenue (48 University Avenue).</string>
    <string name="JefferyInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="JefferyInfo">Jeffery Hall is home to the Department of Mathematics and Statistics. Jeffery Hall is composed of six floors, three above and three below ground.</string>
    <string name="JefferyFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="JefferyFact">Jeffery Hall is named after Ralph L. Jeffery, the Head of Mathematics and Chair of Graduate Studies from 1943 to 1960. The reasoning behind having underground floors in Jeffery Hall was so that it would not detract from the tower of Grant Hall, across the street.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_go_to_ilc">GoToILC</string>
    <string name="title_activity_jeffry_hall_bldg">JeffryHallBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_jeffery_hall_bldg">JefferyHallBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash">splash</string>
    <string name="TourInstructions">Once you are there, click the button below to start your tour. \n\n The black route is a suggested route of a tour around campus. Using your GPS position (the blue marker), follow the route, and click on the markers twice to get more information about each building.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_location21">location21</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About</string>
    <string name="about">QEng Tour was developed by first-year Engineering students as part of a design course project. QEng Tour aims to provide a tour experience to prospective Engineering students and their parents without a tour guide. The tour describes the main uses and interesting facts about each building. In addition, it provides answers to frequently asked questions, as well as relevant contact information.\n\nAll content and images of the Queen’s University campus have been sourced from the Queen’s website.\n\nThe integrated tour makes use of Google Maps\' API.</string>


</resources>
