<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Queens Tour</string>
    <string name="line1">Welcome to the Queens University Tour!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="button1">Take the Tour</string>
    <string name="button2">Map of Campus</string>
    <string name="button3">Gallery</string>
    <string name="button4">Pro Tips</string>
    <string name="button5">F.A.Q.</string>
    <string name="button6">Links and Contacts</string>
    <string name="title_activity_guided_tour">Take the Tour</string>
    <string name="title_activity_campus_map">Map of Campus</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fun_facts">Fun Facts</string>
    <string name="title_activity_faq">Frequently Asked Questions</string>
    <string name="title_activity_links_and_contacts">Links and Contacts</string>
    <string name="title_activity_google_map_of_campus">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_list_of_gallery">ListOfGallery</string>
    <string name="EngTitle">Eng</string>
    //Strings for Links and Contacts Page                                                            <string name="TitleContactsPage">Links and Contacts</string>
    <string name="GenInfo">General Information</string>
    <string name="C1"> Stacy Shane</string>
    <string name="Info1">mgrss@appsci.queensu.ca</string>
    <string name="C2"> Main Reception</string>
    <string name="Info2">reception@appsci.queensu.ca</string>
    <string name="FirstYO">First Year Engineers</string>
    <string name="C3"> Aphra Rogers</string>
    <string name="Info3">firstyr@appsci.queensu.ca</string>
    //FAQ Strings                                                            <string name="TitleFAQPage">Frequently Asked Questions</string>
    <string name="Question1FAQPage">Q) What are all these extra charges I see?</string>
    <string name="Answer1FAQPage"> LALALALALA </string>
    //A) University is expensive. However, some of the costs are actually optional. For example, student fees include a health and dental plan, bus passes, and gym membership. If you'd like, you can opt out of those fees. Details here: "http://myams.org/society/about-your-ams/student-activity-fees"                                                            <string name="Q2FAQPage">hi</string>
    <string name="A2FAQPage">hi</string>
    <string name="Q3FAQPage">hi</string>
    <string name="A3FAQPage">hi</string>
    <string name="Q4FAQPage">hi</string>
    <string name="A4FAQPage">hi</string>
    <string name="Q5FAQPage">hi</string>
    <string name="A5FAQPage">hi</string>
    <string name="title_activity_google_guided_tour">Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_engineering_buildings_menu">EngineeringBuildingsMenu</string>
    <string name="title_activity_non_engineering_buildings_menu">NonEngineeringBuildingsMenu</string>
    <string name="title_activity_food_buildings_menu">FoodBuildingsMenu</string>
    <string name="title_activity_historical_buildings_menu">HistoricalBuildingsMenu</string>
    <string name="title_activity_picture_view_campus_map">PictureViewCampusMap</string>
    <string name="title_activity_picture_view_campus_map2">PictureViewCampusMap2</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_ellis_hall_building">EllisHallBuilding</string>
    <string name="EllisHallLocation">Location: 58 University Avenue, Kingston, Ontario. </string>
    <string name="EllisTitle">Ellis Hall</string>
    <string name="EllisInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="EllisInfo">Ellis Hall, constructed in 1958, is home to the Department of Civil Engineering, the Queen’s Observatory, the GeoEngineering Centre, and the Groundwater and Flows Research Groups. The observatory houses a 16-inch state-of-the-art telescope used to study astrophysics. Ellis Hall is also home to multiple classrooms and an auditorium, where many first year engineering lectures are held. </string>
    <string name="EllisFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="EllisFact">Ellis Hall was one of the first engineering buildings at Queen’s University to be built away from the north-east portion of campus.
Ellis Hall also houses new and innovative classrooms, with interactive displays and unique seating arrangements, both of which allow for increased group work and participation. These classrooms are used for APSC 100 (Engineering Practice) Module 1, a first year engineering course based on group projects. </string>
    <string name="title_activity_chernoff_hall_building">ChernoffHallBuilding</string>
    <string name="ChernoffTitle">Chernoff Hall</string>
    <string name="ChernoffHallLocation">Location:90 Bader Lane, Kingston, Ontario. Located on the south side of Victoria Hall.  </string>
    <string name="ChernoffInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="ChernoffInfo">Chernoff Hall, home to the Department of Chemistry is a new and innovative building composed of both classrooms, laboratory and administrative based sections, and an auditorium/lecture hall that seats 250 people. </string>
    <string name="ChernoffFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="ChernoffFact">Chernoff Hall was built with a substantial contribution from Michael and Dorine Chernoff. Both him and his wife also created the, ‘Chernoff Family Award’, which offers financial assistance to students around Canada who wish to attend Queen’s University.  </string>
    <string name="title_activity_clark_hall_building">ClarkHallBuilding</string>
    <string name="ClarkTitle">Clark Hall</string>
    <string name="ClarkHallLocation">Location: 30 Fifth Field Company Lane, Kingston, Ontario. </string>
    <string name="ClarkInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="ClarkInfo">Clark Hall, home to the Campus Bookstore, and the Clark Hall Pub, was built between 1949 and 1951 with finances paid entirely by engineering students. Clark Hall Pub is located in the top of the building, run by the Engineering Society, and serves as an inviting gathering spot for all students in applied science, and other faculties. </string>
    <string name="ClarkFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="ClarkFact">Clark Hall Pub, first opened as a place for students and faculty to correlate recreationally. With the highly riveting, ‘Ritual’ occurring every Friday afternoon, Clark Hall Pub’s weekly events still serve as long standing traditions amongst members of the engineering faculty. </string>
    <string name="title_activity_dupuis_hall_building">DupuisHallBuilding</string>
    <string name="DupuisTitle">Dupuis Hall</string>
    <string name="DupuisHallLocation">Location: 19 Division Street, Kingston, Ontario. (Attached to the Integrated Learning Centre) </string>
    <string name="DupuisInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="DupuisInfo">Dupuis Hall contains the Campus Computer Sales and Service Store, and the ITservices Main Office. Contains two classrooms and one auditorium. It is home to the department of Chemical Engineering. </string>
    <string name="DupuisFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="DupuisFact">Dupuis Hall was constructed in 1966 and is named after Nathan Fellowes Dupuis, a professor of math at Queens in the early 20th century, also a founder of the Faculty of Engineering and Applied Science. </string>
    <string name="title_activity_goodwin_hall_building">GoodwinHallBuilding</string>
    <string name="GoodwinTitle">Goodwin Hall</string>
    <string name="GoodwinHallLocation">Location:Union and Division Street, Ontario, Kingston.  </string>
    <string name="GoodwinInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="GoodwinInfo">Goodwin Hall is home to the department of Mining Engineering. It was built in 1972 and it was named after William Lawton Goodwin, the first director of the School of Mining and Agriculture, which is the modern day Faculty of Engineering and Applied Science. There are two classrooms in Goodwin Hall, which together, hold a capacity of 106 students. </string>
    <string name="GoodwinFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="GoodwinFact">: The department of Mining Engineering was the first active department in what evolved into the Faculty of Engineering and Applied Science. Goodwin Hall also houses the School of Computing. In June of 2002, a 20 kilowatt solar array was installed on Goodwin’s roof. It was constructed as a learning, teaching, and research tool for Applied Science students. The array produces 18,000 kWh of electricity annually, which is distributed among Walter Light Hall, Goodwin Hall, and the Integrated Learning Centre. </string>
    <string name="title_activity_ilcbuilding">ILCBuilding</string>
    <string name="ILCTitle">Integrated Learning Centre</string>
    <string name="ILCLocation">Location: Union and Division Street, Ontario, Kingston. </string>
    <string name="ILCInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="ILCInfo">The Integrated Learning Centre (ILC) is home to the Faculty of Engineering and Applied Science. It is also called Beamish-Munro Hall.  In addition, the building consists of group rooms, a multimedia facility, a site investigation facility, a design studio, and a prototyping studio and lab facilities. Beamish-Munro Hall was built to meet the needs of a growing multi-disciplinary Engineering faculty, as a model of sustainable construction. </string>
    <string name="ILCFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="ILCFact"> It was named in honor of the families of Robert Beamish (Sci’60) and Donald Munro (Sci’52). In 2005, a year after opening, it was selected as one of the most environmentally advanced buildings in Canada. [12] The ILC is a student-oriented building that was designed in collaboration with students. It serves as a resource to broaden awareness of green building design and environmental sustainability. The facility itself is instrumented as a working laboratory, where students can see structural elements of the building that are usually hidden and monitor systems like air quality, heating, lighting, and cooling using specially designed software, showing how sustainable practices can be incorporated into building design. Inside the front doors is a green wall that filters particles from the air before it is distributed throughout the building. Since 2004, it has won a numerous number of awards.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_innovation_commons_building">InnovationCommonsBuilding</string>
    <string name="ICTitle">Innovation Commons</string>
    <string name="ICInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="ICInfo">The Queen’s Innovation Commons is a new 70,000 square-foot complex that the University is planning to launch to condone graduate students innovative ideas and creations. This building will serve as a cohesive and collaborative learning environment that will help students succeed from an entrepreneurial standpoint. Special laboratories, offices, classrooms, machinery, and equipment will be made available to students to support their learning and expansion of their academic knowledge. The QIC is a new approach to teaching and designing, where students and faculty members have the opportunity to work out complex solutions to dignified problems. The Queen’s Innovation Commons will be equipped with world renowned design studios to support graduate students in their research. Students need to have opportunities and resources available to them to think critically and thrive in the workplace, and that is what is the aim of the QIC. The post secondary world is a competitive environment, but with the help of the Queen’s Innovation Commons, graduate students will have the chance to have their ideas flourish and grow, with support from team members and colleagues. </string>
    <string name="title_activity_mclaughlin_hall_building">MclaughlinHallBuilding</string>
    <string name="MclaughlinTitle">Mclaughlin Hall</string>
    <string name="MclaughlinHallLocation">Location: 130 Stuart Street, Ontario, Kingston. (South side of the intersection of University and Stuart.) </string>
    <string name="MclaughlinInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="MclaughlinInfo">McLaughlin Hall contains 3 classrooms and is home to lectures for Engineers. It is home to the department of Mechanical Engineering. </string>
    <string name="MclaughlinFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="MclaughlinFact">McLaughlin Hall was completed in 1948. It was built on the old site of the Observatory. A story is told that Chancellor Dunning obtained the funds for Dunning hall by passing a note at a board meeting to Col. McLaughlin, which said “Queen’s needs a new mechanical engineering building.”</string>
    <string name="title_activity_miller_hall_building">MillerHallBuilding</string>
    <string name="MillerTitle">Miller Hall</string>
    <string name="MillerHallLocation">Location: 36 Union Street, Ontario, Kingston. (On Union Street opposite the end of Division Street) </string>
    <string name="MillerInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="MillerInfo">Miller Hall, constructed in 1931, is home to the Department of Geological Sciences and Geological Engineering, as well as the Miller Museum of Geology. Miller Hall was greatly expanded in 1973, with the construction of the Bruce Wing. Miller Hall is located in the cluster of engineering buildings in the north east-quarter of campus. </string>
    <string name="MillerFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="MillerFact">Miller Hall hosts many rocks and minerals, as can be learned from APSC 151 (Earth Systems and Engineering), a first year course discussing mainly geology. </string>
    <string name="title_activity_stirling_hall_building">StirlingHallBuilding</string>
    <string name="StirlingTitle">Stirling Hall</string>
    <string name="StirlingHallLocation">Location: 64 Bader Lane, Kingston, Ontario. </string>
    <string name="StirlingInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="StirlingInfo">Stirling Hall is the distinctive round building, home to the Departments of Physics, Engineering Physics and Astronomy. It contains many lecture halls as well as a range of smaller rooms used for labs and tutorials.  </string>
    <string name="StirlingFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="StirlingFact">A notable feature of the building is a Foucault Pendulum, which hangs in the centre of the second floor. The pendulum swings in a pattern and at a speed determined by the rotation of the earth and the latitude of Kingston.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_walter_light_building">WalterLightBuilding</string>
    <string name="WalterTitle">Walter Light Hall</string>
    <string name="WalterHallLocation">Location: North side of Union Street between Barrie and Division. (Kingston, Ontario)  </string>
    <string name="WalterInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="WalterInfo">Walter Light Hall is home to the department of Electrical and Computer Engineering (ECE). The fifth floor of the building includes an Information Processing and Communication Laboratory (IPCL). The research goals of the laboratory are to impact and influence the next generations of wireless communication systems and their application. It provides a unique research training experience for graduate students. In addition to the lab’s own work, they also collaborate with other laboratories at Queen’s, as well as, several other laboratories in Canada, such as the Communications Research Centre in Ottawa. </string>
    <string name="WalterFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="WalterFact">The building is located on the north side of Union Street between Barrie and Division streets. One interesting feature of the building is that every floor is connected to Goodwin Hall. </string>
    <string name="title_activity_ban_building">BanBuilding</string>
    <string name="BanRighTitle">Ban-Righ Cafeteria</string>
    <string name="BanRighLocation">Location: 10 Bader Lane, Kingston, Ontario. </string>
    <string name="BanRighInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="BanRighInfo">Ban Righ Dining Hall is the second largest dining hall on campus . Like Leonard Hall, Ban Righ offers a buffet-style service featuring nutritious entrees, desserts and more. </string>
    <string name="BanRighFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="BanRighFact">Vegetarian and special dietary options are available every meal, and the Queen’s Food site allows students to view weekly menus online. Ban Righ is not open on weekends. </string>
    <string name="title_activity_lazy_building">LazyBuilding</string>
    <string name="LazyTitle">The Lazy Scholar</string>
    <string name="LazyLocation">Location: Located on the lower level of Victoria Hall on 75 Bader Lane, Kingston, Ontario. </string>
    <string name="LazyInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="LazyInfo">The Lazy Scholar is located in the basement of Victoria Hall, and serves as a retail food outlet/cafe for students, especially first years. Featuring flat screen tv’s, pool tables, ping pool tables, a fireplace, and a comfortable lounge, the Lazy Scholar is the go to place for interaction amongst friends. </string>
    <string name="LazyFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="LazyFact">The Lazy Scholar often holds events such as open mic nights, accepts meal plans, and is open late during the week for those night time studying snacks! </string>
    <string name="title_activity_leonard_building">LeonardBuilding</string>
    <string name="LennyTitle">Leonard Hall Cafeteria</string>
    <string name="LennyLocation">Location: 150 Queen’s Crescent, Kingston, Ontario. </string>
    <string name="LennyInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="LennyInfo">Leonard is a student cafeteria on campus. It provides new daily menu options, such as the vegan station, pizza bar, soup and salad bar and more. </string>
    <string name="LennyFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="LennyFact">Largest dining hall on Queen’s campus with over 650 seats. Special lunches and dinners are scheduled at different times throughout the week. For those with a meal plan (mainly first years), this is a great place to grab food. </string>
    <string name="BenidicksonTitle">Agnes Benidickson Field</string>
    <string name="BenidicksonLocation">Location: South side of Fleming Hall, Kingston, Ontario. </string>
    <string name="BenidicksonInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="BenidicksonInfo">Agnes Benidickson Field (AB Field) is a beautiful garden and recreational area to view and walk/sit in.</string>
    <string name="BenidicksonFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="BenidicksonFact">The field is named after Agnes McCausland Benidickson, the first woman Chancellor at Queen\'s University. AB Field is also the main location of Engineering Frosh Week activities and events. </string>
    <string name="GrantTitle">Grant Hall</string>
    <string name="GrantLocation">Location: </string>
    <string name="GrantInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="GrantInfo">Grant</string>
    <string name="GrantFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="GrantFact">Grant</string>
    <string name="NicolTitle">Nicol Hall</string>
    <string name="NicolLocation">Location: </string>
    <string name="NicolInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="NicolInfo">Nicol</string>
    <string name="NicolFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="NicolFact">Nicol</string>
    <string name="KingstonTitle">Kingston Hall</string>
    <string name="KingstonLocation">Location: </string>
    <string name="KingstonInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="KingstonInfo">Kingston</string>
    <string name="KingstonFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="KingstonFact">Kingston</string>
    <string name="SummerhillTitle">Summerhill</string>
    <string name="SummerhillLocation">Location: </string>
    <string name="SummerhillInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="SummerhillInfo">Summerhill</string>
    <string name="SummerhillFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="SummerhillFact">Summerhill</string>
    <string name="TheologicalTitle">Theological Hall</string>
    <string name="TheologicalLocation">Location: </string>
    <string name="TheologicalInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="TheologicalInfo">Theological</string>
    <string name="TheologicalFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="TheologicalFact">Theological</string>
    <string name="ARCTitle">Athletics and Recreation Centre</string>
    <string name="ARCLocation">Location: </string>
    <string name="ARCInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="ARCInfo">ARC Hall</string>
    <string name="ARCFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="ARCFact">ARC Hall</string>
    <string name="DouglasTitle">Douglas Library</string>
    <string name="DouglasLibraryLocation">Location: </string>
    <string name="DouglasInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="DouglasInfo">Douglas</string>
    <string name="DouglasFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="DouglasFact">Douglas</string>
    <string name="GordonTitle">Gordon Hall</string>
    <string name="GordonHallLocation">Location: </string>
    <string name="GordonInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="GordonInfo">Gordon</string>
    <string name="GordonFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="GordonFact">Gordon</string>
    <string name="JDUCTitle">John Deutsch University Centre</string>
    <string name="JDUCLocation">Location: </string>
    <string name="JDUCInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="JDUCInfo">JDUC Hall</string>
    <string name="JDUCFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="JDUCFact">JDUC Hall</string>
    <string name="MacCorryTitle">Mackintosh-Corry Hall</string>
    <string name="MacCorryLocation">Location: </string>
    <string name="MacCorryInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="MacCorryInfo">Mac-Corry</string>
    <string name="MacCorryFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="MacCorryFact">Mac-Corry</string>
    <string name="NixonTitle">Nixon Field</string>
    <string name="NixonLocation">Location: </string>
    <string name="NixonInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="NixonInfo">Nixon</string>
    <string name="NixonFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="NixonFact">Nixon</string>
    <string name="StaufferTitle">Stauffer Library</string>
    <string name="StaufferLibraryLocation">Location: </string>
    <string name="StaufferInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="StaufferInfo">Stauffer</string>
    <string name="StaufferFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="StaufferFact">Stauffer</string>
    <string name="TindallTitle">Tindall Field</string>
    <string name="TindallLocation">Location: </string>
    <string name="TindallInfoTitle">Main Uses</string>
    <string name="TindallInfo">Tindall</string>
    <string name="TindallFactTitle">Interesting Facts</string>
    <string name="TindallFact">Tindall</string>
    <string name="title_activity_arcbldg">ARCBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_douglas_bldg">DouglasBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_gordon_bldg">GordonBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_jducbldg">JDUCBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_mac_corry_bldg">MacCorryBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_nixon_field_bldg">NixonFieldBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_stauffer_bldg">StaufferBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tindall_bldg">TindallBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_benidickson_bldg">BenidicksonBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_grant_hall_bldg">GrantHallBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_nicol_hall_bldg">NicolHallBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_kingston_hall_bldg">KingstonHallBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_summerhill_bldg">SummerhillBldg</string>
    <string name="title_activity_theological_hall_bldg">TheologicalHallBldg</string>
</resources>
